[{"difficulty": 0, "chunk": 0, "question": "\uc77c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: arbeitete", "answer": "\ufeffarbeiten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:40:14.857971", "learned": true, "info2": "Partizip II: gearbeitet"}, {"difficulty": 0, "chunk": 0, "question": "\uc778\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: begr\u00fc\u00dfte", "answer": "begr\u00fc\u00dfen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:40:14.858024", "learned": true, "info2": "Partizip II: begr\u00fc\u00dft"}, {"difficulty": 0, "chunk": 0, "question": "\ubd88\ub9ac\uc6b0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hie\u00df", "answer": "hei\u00dfen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:40:14.858043", "learned": true, "info2": "Partizip II: gehei\u00dfen"}, {"difficulty": 0, "chunk": 0, "question": "\uc624\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kam", "answer": "kommen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:40:14.858059", "learned": true, "info2": "Partizip II: gekommen"}, {"difficulty": 0, "chunk": 0, "question": "\ucca8\uc0ad\ud558\ub2e4, \uace0\uce58\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: korrigierte", "answer": "korrigieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:40:14.858073", "learned": true, "info2": "Partizip II: korrigiert"}, {"difficulty": 0, "chunk": 0, "question": "\uadf8\ub9ac\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: malte", "answer": "malen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:40:14.858087", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gemalt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 1, "question": "\uc54c\ub9de\ub2e4, \uc5b4\uc6b8\ub9ac\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: passte", "answer": "passen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115664", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gepasst"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 1, "question": "\ubaa8\uc73c\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sammelte", "answer": "sammeln", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115674", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gesammelt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 1, "question": "~\uc774\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: war", "answer": "sein", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115683", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gewesen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 1, "question": "\uad50\ud658\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: tauschte", "answer": "tauschen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115692", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getauscht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 1, "question": "\uc18c\uac1c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stellte...vor", "answer": "vorstellen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115702", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: vorgestellt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 1, "question": "\uc2dc\uc791\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: begann", "answer": "beginnen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115711", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: begonnen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 2, "question": "\ubc29\ubb38\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: besuchte", "answer": "besuchen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115720", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: besucht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 2, "question": "\ud544\uc694\ub85c \ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brauchte", "answer": "brauchen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115729", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gebraucht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 2, "question": "\ucc3e\ub2e4, \uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fand", "answer": "finden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115738", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gefunden"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 2, "question": "\uc791\ub3d9\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: funktionierte", "answer": "funktionieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115749", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: funktioniert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 2, "question": "\uc8fc\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gab", "answer": "geben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115759", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gegeben"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 2, "question": "\ucc44\uc6cc \ub123\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erg\u00e4nzte", "answer": "erg\u00e4nzen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115768", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: erg\u00e4nzt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 3, "question": "~\uc758 \ub9c8\uc74c\uc5d0 \ub4e4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gefiel", "answer": "gefallen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115778", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gefallen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 3, "question": "\uac00\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: ging", "answer": "gehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115788", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gegangen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 3, "question": "\uae30\ucd08\ub85c \ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gr\u00fcndete", "answer": "gr\u00fcnden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115797", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gegr\u00fcndet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 3, "question": "\uc548\ubd80\ub97c \uc804\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gr\u00fc\u00dfte", "answer": "gr\u00fc\u00dfen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115809", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gegr\u00fc\u00dft"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 3, "question": "\uac00\uc9c0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hatte", "answer": "haben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115819", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gehabt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 3, "question": "\uc54c\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kannte", "answer": "kennen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115828", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gekannt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 4, "question": "\ubc30\uc6b0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lernte", "answer": "lernen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115837", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelernt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 4, "question": "\ud558\ub2e4, \ub9cc\ub4e4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: machte", "answer": "machen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115847", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gemacht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 4, "question": "\uacc4\ud68d\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: plante", "answer": "planen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115856", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geplant"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 4, "question": "\ucda4\ucd94\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: tanzte", "answer": "tanzen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115865", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getanzt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 4, "question": "\uc77d\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: las", "answer": "lesen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115874", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelesen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 4, "question": "\uc804\ud654\ub97c \uac78\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: telefonierte", "answer": "telefonieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115883", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: telefoniert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 5, "question": "\ubcf4\uc5ec\uc8fc\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: zeigte", "answer": "zeigen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115893", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gezeigt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 5, "question": "\uba39\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: a\u00df", "answer": "essen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115904", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gegessen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 5, "question": "\ub9c8\uc2dc\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: trank", "answer": "trinken", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115913", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getrunken"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 5, "question": "\ud611\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: besprach", "answer": "besprechen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115922", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: besprochen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 5, "question": "\uc774\uc57c\uae30\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erz\u00e4hlte", "answer": "erz\u00e4hlen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115931", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: erz\u00e4hlt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 5, "question": "\ube44\uc6a9\uc774 \ub4e4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kostete", "answer": "kosten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115941", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gekostet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 6, "question": "\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: tat", "answer": "tun", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115950", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getan"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 6, "question": "\ube44\uad50\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verglich", "answer": "vergleichen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115959", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: verglichen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 6, "question": "\ubc1b\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bekam", "answer": "bekommen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115968", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: bekommen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 6, "question": "\uc9c0\ubd88\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bezahlte", "answer": "bezahlen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115977", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: bezahlt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 6, "question": "\ud5c8\ub77d\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erlaubte", "answer": "erlauben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115986", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: erlaubt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 6, "question": "\ud0c0\uace0 \uac00\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fuhr", "answer": "fahren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115995", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gefahren"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 7, "question": "\uae30\ub150\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: feierte", "answer": "feiern", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116006", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gefeiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 7, "question": "\uc6b4\ubc18\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: trug", "answer": "tragen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116016", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getragen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 7, "question": "\ubca8\uc774 \uc6b8\ub9ac\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: klingelte", "answer": "klingeln", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116025", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geklingelt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 7, "question": "\ub3c4\ucc29\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kam\u2026an", "answer": "ankommen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116034", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: angekommen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 7, "question": "\uacbd\ud0c4\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bewunderte", "answer": "bewundern", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116043", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: bewundert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 7, "question": "\uc870\uc9c1\ud558\ub2e4, \ud615\uc131\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: organisierte", "answer": "organisieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116053", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: organisiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 8, "question": "\ubc1c\uc0dd\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: passierte", "answer": "passieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116062", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: passiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 8, "question": "\uccad\uc18c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: putzte", "answer": "putzen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116071", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geputzt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 8, "question": "\ucc3d\uc870\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schuf", "answer": "schaffen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116080", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geschaffen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 8, "question": "\uc790\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schlief", "answer": "schlafen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116091", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geschlafen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 8, "question": "\ubc14\ub77c\ubcf4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schaute", "answer": "schauen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116100", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geschaut"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 8, "question": "\ubcf4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sah", "answer": "sehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116109", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gesehen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 9, "question": "\ucd94\ub77d\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: st\u00fcrzte", "answer": "st\u00fcrzen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116118", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gest\u00fcrzt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 9, "question": "\ucc3e\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: suchte", "answer": "suchen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116127", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gesucht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 9, "question": "\ub9cc\ub098\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: traf", "answer": "treffen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116136", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getroffen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 9, "question": "\uc54c\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wusste", "answer": "wissen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116145", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gewusst"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 9, "question": "\uc6d0\ud558\ub2e4, \ubc14\ub77c\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: w\u00fcnschte", "answer": "w\u00fcnschen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116154", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gew\u00fcnscht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 9, "question": "\ub370\ub9ac\ub7ec \uac00\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: holte...ab", "answer": "abholen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116163", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: abgeholt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 10, "question": "\uc5f4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: machte...auf", "answer": "aufmachen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116175", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: aufgemacht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 10, "question": "\uc548\ub418\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: ging...aus", "answer": "ausgehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116184", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: ausgegangen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 10, "question": "\uc790\ub974\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schnitt", "answer": "schneiden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116193", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geschnitten"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 10, "question": "\ud1b5\ud654\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: rief...an", "answer": "anrufen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116202", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: angerufen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 10, "question": "\ub300\ub2f5\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: antwortete", "answer": "antworten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116211", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geantwortet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 10, "question": "\uc751\uc2dc\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schaute...an", "answer": "anschauen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116220", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: angeschaut"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 11, "question": "\ub178\ub798\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sang", "answer": "singen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116229", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gesungen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 11, "question": "~\ub85c \ubcf4\uc774\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sah...aus", "answer": "aussehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116238", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: ausgesehen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 11, "question": "\uc0ac\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: benutzte", "answer": "benutzen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116247", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: benutzt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 11, "question": "\ubb18\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: beschrieb", "answer": "beschreiben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116256", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: beschrieben"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 11, "question": "\uba38\ubb34\ub974\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: blieb", "answer": "bleiben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116269", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geblieben"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 11, "question": "\uc2dc\uac04\uc774 \uac78\ub9ac\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dauerte", "answer": "dauern", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116281", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gedauert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 12, "question": "\uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dachte", "answer": "denken", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116291", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gedacht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 12, "question": "\uc0e4\uc6cc\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: duschte", "answer": "duschen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116300", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geduscht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 12, "question": "\ub3c4\ub2ec\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erreichte", "answer": "erreichen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116309", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: erreicht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 12, "question": "\ubbff\ub2e4, \uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: glaubte", "answer": "glauben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116318", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geglaubt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 12, "question": "\uc815\ubcf4\ub97c \uc8fc\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: informierte", "answer": "informieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116327", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: informiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 12, "question": "\ub370\ub9ac\uace0 \uc624\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brachte\u2026mit", "answer": "mitbringen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116336", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: mitgebracht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 13, "question": "\ucd9c\ubc1c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fuhr\u2026ab", "answer": "abfahren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116345", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: abgefahren"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 13, "question": "\uc8fc\ubb38\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bestellte", "answer": "bestellen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116358", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: bestellt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 13, "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: redete", "answer": "reden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116369", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geredet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 13, "question": "\ube44\uac00 \uc624\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: regnete", "answer": "regnen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116378", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geregnet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 13, "question": "\uc218\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: reparierte", "answer": "reparieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116387", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: repariert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 13, "question": "\uc549\uc544 \uc788\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sa\u00df", "answer": "sitzen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116396", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gesessen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 14, "question": "\uc11c \uc788\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stand", "answer": "stehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116405", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gestanden"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 14, "question": "\uce21\uc815\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: ma\u00df", "answer": "messen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116415", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gemessen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 14, "question": "\uc2dc\uac04\uc744 \ubcf4\ub0b4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verbrachte", "answer": "verbringen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116424", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: verbracht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 14, "question": "\uc78a\uc5b4\ubc84\ub9ac\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verga\u00df", "answer": "vergessen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116435", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: vergessen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 14, "question": "\uc0ac\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verwendete", "answer": "verwenden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116447", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: verwendet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 14, "question": "\uad50\uccb4\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wechselte", "answer": "wechseln", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116456", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gewechselt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 15, "question": "\ubd80\uc871\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fehlte", "answer": "fehlen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116465", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gefehlt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 15, "question": "\uc2dc\uc791\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fing...an", "answer": "anfangen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116474", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: angefangen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 15, "question": "\uc785\uc5b4\ubcf4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: probierte...an", "answer": "anprobieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116483", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: anprobiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 15, "question": "\ubc00\uce58\ub2e4, \uac74\ubc30\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sto\u00dfte...an", "answer": "ansto\u00dfen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116495", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: angesto\u00dft"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 15, "question": "\uc8fc\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: passte\u2026auf", "answer": "aufpassen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116506", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: aufgepasst"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 15, "question": "\uc218\ucd9c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: f\u00fchrte...aus", "answer": "ausf\u00fchren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116515", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: ausgef\u00fchrt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 16, "question": "\uc758\ubbf8\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bedeutete", "answer": "bedeuten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116526", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: bedeutet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 16, "question": "\uac00\uc9c0\uace0 \uc624\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brachte", "answer": "bringen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116538", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gebracht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 16, "question": "\uad6c\ub9e4\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kaufte", "answer": "kaufen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116547", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gekauft"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 16, "question": "\ubcf5\uc6a9\uc2dc\ud0a4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gab...ein", "answer": "eingeben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116556", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: eingegeben"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 16, "question": "\ucd08\ub300\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lud...ein", "answer": "einladen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116565", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: eingeladen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 16, "question": "\uc6a9\uc11c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: entschuldigte", "answer": "entschuldigen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116573", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: entschuldigt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 17, "question": "\uc124\uba85\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erkl\u00e4rte", "answer": "erkl\u00e4ren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116582", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: erkl\u00e4rt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 17, "question": "TV\ub97c \ubcf4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sah...fern", "answer": "fernsehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116591", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: ferngesehen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 17, "question": "\ubd99\uc7a1\ub2e4, \uace0\uc9d1\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hielt\u2026fest", "answer": "festhalten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116600", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: festgehalten"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 17, "question": "\ub3d5\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: half", "answer": "helfen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116610", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geholfen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 17, "question": "\uac00\uc838\uc624\ub2e4, \uaebc\ub0b4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: holte", "answer": "holen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116621", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geholt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 17, "question": "\ubcf5\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kopierte", "answer": "kopieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116631", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: kopiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 18, "question": "\ubbf8\uc18c\ub97c \uc9d3\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: l\u00e4chelte", "answer": "l\u00e4cheln", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116643", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gel\u00e4chelt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 18, "question": "\uba54\uc77c\uc744 \ubcf4\ub0b4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: mailte", "answer": "mailen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116652", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gemailt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 18, "question": "\ubb38\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fragte\u2026nach", "answer": "nachfragen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116662", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: nachgefragt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 18, "question": "\ucde8\ud558\ub2e4, \uac00\uc9c0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: nahm", "answer": "nehmen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116670", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: genommen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 18, "question": "\uba85\uba85\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: nannte", "answer": "nennen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116680", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: genannt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 18, "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sagte", "answer": "sagen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116689", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gesagt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 19, "question": "\ucd94\ucc9c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: empfahl", "answer": "empfehlen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116697", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: empfohlen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 19, "question": "\ub0a0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: flog", "answer": "fliegen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116706", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geflogen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 19, "question": "\uafc8\uafb8\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: t\u00e4umte", "answer": "tr\u00e4umen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116715", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getr\u00e4umt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 19, "question": "\ucd94\uce21\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: vermutete", "answer": "vermuten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116728", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: vermutet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 19, "question": "\uc2dc\ub3c4\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: versuchte", "answer": "versuchen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116737", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: versucht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 19, "question": "\uae30\ub2e4\ub9ac\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wartete", "answer": "warten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116746", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gewartet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 20, "question": "\ub05d\ub0b4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: beendete", "answer": "beenden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116755", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: beendet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 20, "question": "\ub2ec\ub9ac\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lief", "answer": "laufen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116764", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelaufen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 20, "question": "\uac10\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dankte", "answer": "danken", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116776", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gedankt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 20, "question": "\ud558\uac8c \ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lie\u00df", "answer": "lassen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116788", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelassen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 20, "question": "\uc815\ub9ac\uc815\ub3c8\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: r\u00e4umte...auf", "answer": "aufr\u00e4umen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116797", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: aufger\u00e4umt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 20, "question": "\ub4e3\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: h\u00f6rte", "answer": "h\u00f6ren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116806", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geh\u00f6rt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 21, "question": "\ubab0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: trieb", "answer": "treiben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116818", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: getrieben"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 21, "question": "\uacb0\ud63c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: heiratete", "answer": "heiraten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116827", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geheiratet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 21, "question": "\uc6c3\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lachte", "answer": "lachen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116836", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelacht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 21, "question": "\uc0b4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lebte", "answer": "leben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116845", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelebt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 21, "question": "\uc5ec\ud589\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: reiste", "answer": "reisen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116856", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gereist"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 21, "question": "\ub9db\uc774 \ub098\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schmeckte", "answer": "schmecken", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116865", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geschmeckt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 22, "question": "\uc8fd\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: starb", "answer": "sterben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116875", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gestorben"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 22, "question": "\uc804\uacf5\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: studierte", "answer": "studieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116883", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: studiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 22, "question": "\uc774\ud574\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verstand", "answer": "verstehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116892", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: verstanden"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 22, "question": "\uc218\uc601\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schwamm", "answer": "schwimmen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116903", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geschwommen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 22, "question": "\uc218\uc5c5\uc744 \ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: unterrichtete", "answer": "unterrichten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116915", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: unterrichtet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 22, "question": "\ub418\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wurde", "answer": "werden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116924", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geworden"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 23, "question": "\uc774\uae30\ub2e4, \uc5bb\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gewann", "answer": "gewinnen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116933", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gewonnen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 23, "question": "\uc0ac\ub791\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: liebte", "answer": "lieben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116942", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geliebt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 23, "question": "\ud6d4\uce58\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stahl", "answer": "stehlen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116951", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gestohlen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 23, "question": "\ud574\ubcf4\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: probierte", "answer": "probieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116962", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: probiert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 23, "question": "\uac12\uc744 \uce58\ub974\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: zahlte", "answer": "zahlen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116971", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gezahlt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 23, "question": "\uc7a5\uc2dd\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dekorierte", "answer": "dekorieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116980", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: dekoriert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 24, "question": "\uc120\ubb3c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schenkte", "answer": "schenken", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116990", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geschenkt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 24, "question": "\uae68\ub2e4, \ubd80\ub7ec\uc9c0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brach", "answer": "brechen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117001", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gebrochen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 24, "question": "\uc608\uc57d\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: buchte", "answer": "buchen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117010", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gebucht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 24, "question": "\uac70\uc9d3\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: log", "answer": "l\u00fcgen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117019", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelogen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 24, "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sprach", "answer": "sprechen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117028", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gesprochen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 24, "question": "\uac78\ub2e4, \uac78\ub824\uc788\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hing", "answer": "h\u00e4ngen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117038", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gehangen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 25, "question": "\ub215\ud788\ub2e4, \ub193\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lag", "answer": "liegen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117049", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelegen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 25, "question": "\ub193\uc5ec\uc788\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: legte", "answer": "legen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117058", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gelegt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 25, "question": "\ub180\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: spielte", "answer": "spielen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117068", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gespielt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 25, "question": "\uc138\uc6cc\ub450\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stellte", "answer": "stellen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117076", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gestellt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 25, "question": "\ud569\uaca9\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bestand", "answer": "bestehen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117085", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: bestanden"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 25, "question": "\uc694\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kochte", "answer": "kochen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117096", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gekocht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 26, "question": "\ub098\ub204\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: teilte", "answer": "teilen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117105", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geteilt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 26, "question": "\uc53b\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wusch", "answer": "waschen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117114", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gewaschen"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 26, "question": "\ubd88\uc5d0 \ud0c0\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brannte", "answer": "brennen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117123", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gebrannt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 26, "question": "\ub4f1\ubc18\ud558\ub2e4, \uac77\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wanderte", "answer": "wandern", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117134", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gewandert"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 26, "question": "\ubc88\uc5ed\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: \u00fcbersetzte", "answer": "\u00fcbersetzen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117144", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: \u00fcbersetzt"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 26, "question": "\ub2f4\ubc30\ub97c \ud53c\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: rauchte", "answer": "rauchen", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117153", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: geraucht"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 27, "question": "\uc5f0\uae30\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verschob", "answer": "verschieben", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117162", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: verschoben"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 27, "question": "\uc5f0\uacb0\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verband", "answer": "verbinden", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117171", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: verbunden"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 27, "question": "\uad6c\ucd9c\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: rettete", "answer": "retten", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117182", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: gerettet"}, {"difficulty": 2, "chunk": 27, "question": "\uc0b0\ucc45\ud558\ub2e4", "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: spazierte", "answer": "spazieren", "date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117200", "learned": false, "info2": "Partizip II: spaziert"}]